This video will introduce the functions related to the mode and editor for you to improve.
First of all, it is an improvement in terms of printing and distribution. We significantly improved the cost and calculation process.
In this update, now you can automatically calculate the average production of each piece of clothing according to the material data and monitor the cost of each piece of clothing.
This update makes it easier for you to calculate and manage production costs directly in the software.
If you want to check the cost information, please click on the material list under the top main menu.
You can see that the screen central fabric project list has been newly added to the single-click cost list on the right.
And below the number, there is also a gray number that shows the amount of each piece.
Open the printing and distribution, click on the material setting icon in the tool bar.
Then you can see the information menu.
Under the information menu, you can see that the average length of each piece of clothing has been newly added.
Set the print number to 5 and the width to 1200 mm.
Click on the print all fabric icon to print.
Check the value again, you can see that it has been updated according to the print result.
In order to match the final cost, we open the material list editor again.
You can see the cost of each piece of fabric, which has been calculated according to the material data just processed in the print distribution.
At this time, I want to modify the price of the fabric and unit.
You can find the small ruler icon at the top.
Enter the user's self-definition and choose to modify it to RMB.
Modify the volume unit to meters.
Adjust the price of each meter.
At this time, the total cost has been updated.
For the cost of the unit, you need to click on the update button in the upper left corner and update.
Adjust the price of the other piece of fabric and update.
From this version, when you print, the line direction is set to two or four directions.
You can set the same-piece clothing in the same direction.
This function ensures that all the pieces of the same-piece clothing in the same-piece clothing maintain the same line direction.
First, open the print.
Let's change the line direction of the attribute editor to two or four directions.
The same-piece and same-piece options that were previously in use can now be used.
Click to open this option.
Then set the number of clothing as the number of numbers.
Select the number of numbers to be divided.
Set the number of number keys that need to be typed.
Here I will type two keys, XSM and XL.
Click on the print icon to start printing.
After the print is finished,
Open the display number random color in the vertical menu bar.
And display the size of the number.
Convenient for checking the direction of clothing.
Although the overall print is in line with the set line direction,
But you can see that all the pieces of the same-piece clothing are also in the same direction.
Now you can choose from the attribute editor of the print.
Click on the print icon.
In the editor,
Choose to set the print line,
Print line or base line as reference lines for efficient execution of the print.
Click on the print setting.
You can find in the attribute editor.
The new print calculation of the print menu.
You can use the download menu to select the reference line you need.
At this time, the print is selected.
You can see that the result of the print is calculated according to the print of the print.
When the print has a print,
It will also default the print as the print line.
Now set the option to print line.
Execute the print again.
You can see that the print will be calculated according to the print line.
The last is the base line option.
Since the external CAD print is imported as DXF format,
The print is displayed in the form of a base line.
Select this option and run the print.
The print will run according to the base line set on the print.
So in this case,
Use the base line option to make the exact print.
Switch back to the print option print again.
Select the print of the print,
then the different print options on the print underneath.
Press the breath while holding down the Eden onboarding.
Now select includes,
from the command bar,
To send a print pattern to the print set.
Once the exact measurement distance is displayed, only one measurement value is displayed at a time.
When you click on another point, the previous measurement value will be automatically deleted, and a new measurement will be started.
Once again, click on the roll icon to exit this function.
Finally, I will introduce you to the shortcut key to add a rotating board.
After clicking on the board, the mouse will stop on the rotation option in the menu.
You can see that each rotation direction and angle correspond to the shortcut key.
Please select a board that needs to be rotated one or more times.
Press the Ctrl key and press the right arrow key to rotate the board clockwise 45 degrees.
Press the left arrow key to rotate the board counterclockwise 45 degrees.
When you want to rotate in a larger angle, you can press the right arrow key to rotate counterclockwise 90 degrees,
or press the left arrow key to rotate counterclockwise 90 degrees.
When you want to rotate in a larger angle, you can press the right arrow key to rotate counterclockwise 90 degrees.
This is a guide to help you work with the animation environment and improve the accuracy.
Animation Time Rectangle Marker
In animation projects, time control is important.
These markers are like the numbers on the time axis.
Let's learn how to use these markers to simplify your production process.
First, we need to enter the bottom of the screen.
We need to enter the animation editor at the bottom of the screen.
Check the time axis and the area that shows your real number.
If you want to add a precise moment to view and mark the animation,
All you need to do is right-click on the time axis and click on the animation mark group in the right menu.
At this time, an animation mark dialogue box will pop up.
You can specify a specific name for the mark here.
For example, from here, and you can set a precise real number.
After pressing OK, stop the mouse on the mark indicator.
You will see a pop-up window.
It contains a specific name and position for quick reference.
If you want to edit the animation mark,
You can right-click it and select Edit or Double-click.
By dragging the mark, you can adjust its position.
To copy, paste and delete the animation mark,
You can right-click the animation mark again and select the operation you need.
Or use the shortcut Ctrl-C, Ctrl-V and Delete to speed up the operation.
This is how to use a new animation mark to organize your animation.
And better communicate with your team.
You can ensure that every frame in the animation is in its proper position.
I hope this video helps you.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.